Let us listen to what Prophet T.B. Joshua said about the Kenyan elections on Sunday 1st January, 2017.
Let us hear the voice of God.
Thank you, sir. You have answered all of my questions as to why I am here.
Now, since 2017 is a wonderful year, I love my nation, Kenya, and we are having elections.
I am asking that God visits me in dreams, so that I know how to pray about my nation.
God bless you, sir.
You want to take me back to what I have written.
Even your country is one of the countries that is inside the paper there.
If I may tell you just a bit of what is inside that paper.
They will be very, very close like this
and it will be difficult to call.
I will not say more than that.
Can you see? When something is close like this, and it will be difficult to call...
So, I don't want to go back to what is in the paper
because it's one of the things in the paper.
It will be very close like this -
the opposition and the ruling.
It will be very, very difficult to call.
From there - I will not be able to say more than that.
I am not here for that now.
So, therefore, what can you expect from there?
So, I will see you. Thank you.
So, you love your nation so much?